elecard.com 2019-03-07

# Privacy Policy | Elecard: Video Compression Guru

Elecard takes the protection of your data and information very seriously. When you use Elecard’s Services, Elecard Software or Web Site (www.elecard.com), you trust us with your data and information. This Privacy Policy describes the types of data we collect, why we collect it and what we do with it. This is important.

 **1\. Your privacy**

Elecard Devices, CJSC and its Controlled Subsidiaries (“Elecard”) is committed to ensuring the privacy of your data and information, and will hold all personal information collected in association with Elecard in accordance with the requirements of the Privacy Policy.

 **2\. Information about you and your activities that we collect**

We collect the content and other information you provide when you use our Web Site and Services, where allowed by law, including when you register, sign up for an account, create or share, and message or communicate with others (including Elecard’s employees). We also collect contact information you provide if you upload, sync or import this information from a device. This can include information in or about the content you provide. We also collect information about how you use our Web Site and Services, such as the types of content you view or engage with or the frequency and duration of your activities.

 **3\. Use of information**

Your information will only be used to:

  * develop and improve our Web Site and the Software and Services, to develop new products and services; and/or
  * assess and process your application for Elecard’s Services and Web Site, including by sharing your information with third party agencies for the purposes of analysis; and/or
  * provide Elecard’s Services to you; and/or
  * conduct market research and generate and provide statistical analysis and rating information; and/or
  * comply with laws (including court orders and subpoenas).

We will only use personal information (such as your mobile phone number and e-mail address) to communicate with you about our Products and Services, send you marketing communications, newsletters and let you know about our policies and terms, and for other similar purposes.

 **4\. Disclosure of information**

We will not disclose any information you provide to any third party except:

  * to relevant authorities, parties and/or applicable intellectual property rights holders (or their representatives) if we consider that you are in breach of Elecard's rights; or
  * where required, or permitted, by law.

 **5\. Your consent**

By accessing and browsing our Web Site and/or using or applying for the Services, you consent to the collection, use, disclosure, storage and processing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **6\. Information about payments**

If you use our Web Site and Services for purchases or financial transactions (like when you buy something on Web Site, make a purchase), we collect information about the purchase or transaction. This includes your payment information, such as your credit or debit card number and other card information, and other account and authentication information, as well as billing, shipping and contact details.

 **7\. Access to, editing and deleting information**

7.1 You can delete your account any time

7.2 You can update your information through your account profile settings. If you believe that personal information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or inaccurate, then you may request us to amend it. Additionally, you may request access to any personal information we hold about you at any time by contacting us.

 **8\. Security of information, Storage and processing of information**

Elecard has implemented commercially reasonable measures to protect the data and information we collect about you from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Be aware that despite any amount of effort, no data security measures can guarantee security or confidentiality. You should take prudent measures to protect your information (as defined in Section 9). Elecard will store and process your information in the USA or in any other country in which Elecard maintains facilities for doing so. Information may therefore be transferred outside of the USA. By providing us with your data and information, including (where applicable) personally identifiable information, you consent to such transfer, storage, and processing of your information anywhere in the world. Some foreign jurisdictions may have data protection laws less stringent than those of your home jurisdiction.

 **9\. Account security**

9.1 You must keep any login, password or account information relating to your use of this Web Site secure at all times.

9.2 To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of any information supplied by you, Elecard has put in place physical, electronic and managerial processes to protect your information. Additionally, all user information stored on this Web Site is protected from unauthorised access through the use of secure login information and other security procedures.

9.3 Elecard is not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.

 **10\. Links to external websites**

This website may contain links to external websites. Any access to and use of such external websites is not governed by this Privacy Policy. Elecard is not responsible for the privacy policies of any such external websites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Elecard.

 **11\. Cookies Policy**

In this Cookie Policy, we refer to these technologies, which include cookies, pixels, web beacons, Local Storage Objects and gifs, collectively as "cookies".

11.1 Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Web Site and Services, while others are used to enable a faster log-in process or to allow us to track your activities at our Web Site and Service. A cookie file is created by the Website browsing and is transmitted and processed by the Web browser software of your computer. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you have the right to accept or stop cookies from being stored on your device at any time by modifying the settings in your web browser to reflect your cookie preferences.

11.2 We use cookies and other tracking mechanisms to track information about your use of our Web Site or Services. We may combine this information with other personal information we collect from you. We use Cookies to obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Web Site. We use cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about user activity.

11.3 We may use Local Storage Objects to store your Web Site preferences and to personalize your visit. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer’s hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on web pages. We may use clear GIFs, in connection with our Web Site to, among other things, track the activities of Web Site visitors, help us manage content, and compile statistics about Web Site usage. We use clear GIFs in HTML e-mails to our customers, to help us track e-mail response rates, identify when our e-mails are viewed, and track whether our e-mails are forwarded. If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending us email.

 **12\. Respond to legal requests**

We may access, preserve and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so. This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of the USA where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards.

 **13\. Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy from time to time, with or without notice to you. Such amendments will be effective immediately upon the posting of the amended Privacy Policy on this Web Site. You agree to check this Privacy Policy before continuing to use our Services/Web Site. Your continued use of the Web Site, Software, or Services following such an update to this Privacy Policy on the Web Site indicates your acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy.

 **Contact US**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, we can be reached via e-mail at [legal@elecard.ru](mailto:legal@elecard.ru)
